Launches are ongoing across Europe and the Middle East.
And we'll see further expansion in the second half post the EMEA, Japan, and Swiss approvals.
Now, importantly, in chronic inducible urticaria, we presented our REMIND data supporting remibrutinib
as the potential as the first targeted therapy for chronic inducible urticaria.
We had early and broad efficacy with onset as early as week two in the two additional largest subtypes,
consistent 12-week responses versus placebo.
So we're on track for the FDA approval in SD, which is the most common Sindhu subtype,
two-thirds of Sindhu patients.
And then we'll have global filings across all three subtypes later this year.
Just as a reminder, we estimate in the U.S. there's about 100,000 Sindhu patients
that are uncontrolled with antihistamines with no other treatment options.
So this is a significant expansion in the population that can be helped by Rapsido.
Now, turning to slide 14, we also presented some updated data on Yonalimab,
showing the favorable SI benefits of the medicine and longer-term follow-up.
And we remain on track for a U.S. launch in Stogen's disease,
in the second half.
So you can see on the left-hand side of this chart, in our pooled Neptunus data,
you can see the consistent benefits in SDI, statistically significant,
versus the placebo arm across both studies when pooled,
demonstrating the benefits we see with the medicine.
And then, as well, we presented 108-week long-term extension data,
which showed that we can maintain the benefits of Yonalimab over time,
and it also was supported by clinically meaningful improvements
for the placebo crossover group when crossing over onto the active arm.
Also, throughout all of these long-term follow-ups,
we see a favorable safety profile, no increase in adverse events.
So this supports Yonalimab's multi-blockbuster potential.
We're on track for the ITP first-line readout in the second half of 2026.
The SLE and lupus nephritis phase 3 readouts in 2027.
And this is successful.
stomach sclerosis phase 2 rate out as well in 2027. So turning to slide 15, I want to provide
an update on two of the acquired programs from Abidity. First with the Delzota, we achieved our